Finding Aid for Alumni Association (University of Michigan) records, 1845-2001
Bentley Historical Library
- Alumni Societies, 1951-2001 (with gaps)
  - University of Michigan Black Alumni (UMBA), 1976-2000 (with gaps)
    - Reunion of Black Graduates (RBG), 1977-2000 (with gaps); undated
      - Evaluation Forms and Surveys, 1986-ca.1993 (with gaps) (Box 168)
      - Mailing List, 1977-1994 (Box 168)
      - Minority Alumni Program Information Package Index, ca. 1986-1987 (Box 168)
      - Reunions, 1990-2000
        - 14th Annual, 1990 (Box 168)
        - 15th Annual, 1991 (Box 168)
        - 16th Annual, 1992 (Box 168)
        - 17th Annual, 1993 (Box 168)
        - 18th Annual, 1994 (Box 168)
        - 19th Annual, 1995 (Box 168)
        - 20th Annual, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 168)
        - 21st Annual, 1997 (Box 168)
        - 22nd Annual, 1998 (Box 168)
        - 23rd Annual, 1999; undated (Box 168)
        - 24th Annual, 1999-2000 (Box 168)
  - Basketball Letter Winners, 1989-1990 (Box 155)
  - Business School Alumni Society, 1989-1990 (Box 155)
  - College of Architecture and Urban Planning, 1983 (Box 155)
  - College of Pharmacy, 1981-1982 (Box 155)
  - Dental Hygienists, 1956-1989; 2 folders (Box 155)
    (see also scrapbooks in Box 160)
  - Education, 1975-1984; 5 folders (Box 155)
  - Emeritus Club, 1961-1965 (Box 155)
  - Korean Alumni Society, 1990 (Box 155)
  - Medical Center Alumni Society, 1970-1985 (Box 155)
  - Medical Technology, 1951-1978 (Box 155)
  - Michigan Black Law Alumni Society, 1976 (Box 155)
  - School of Dentistry, 1959-1989
    - General
      - 1959-1964 (Box 155)
      - 1966-1974 (Box 155)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 155)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 155)
      - 1983-1989 (Box 155)
    - Opinion Survey, 1982 (Box 155)
    - Visiting Committee, 1972-1989 (Box 155)
  - School of Education, 1975-1991
    - 1975-1984, 5 folders (Box 155)
    - 1984-1991, 3 folders (Box 155)
  - School of Library and Information Science, 1971-1987; 3 folders (Box 156)
  - School of Music, 1975-1980; 3 folders (Box 156)
  - School of Natural Resources, 1976-1984; 8 folders (Box 156)
  - School of Nursing, 1955-1990 (Box 156)
  - School of Public Health, 1963-1991; 3 folders (Box 156)
- Classes and Reunions, 1870-1951
  The series Classes (Boxes 97-104; and box 118) contains information on classes and individual graduates from 1870 to 1909. Documentation includes reunion information, class "records" detailing the status of members of particular classes as well as obituary information on deceased class members. Information on classes is scattered throughout the record group. Several folders of emeritus reunion classes also pertain to various classes. Related material on classes from 1894 to 1963 is located in the Class Reunion Files series (Boxes 148-154).
  - 1870-1891 (Box 97)
    (see also box 134 in Photographs: Class Reunions series)
  - 1894-1895 (Box 98)
  - 1896-1898 (Box 99)
  - 1899-1901 (Box 100)
  - 1901-1904 (Box 101)
  - 1904-1906 (Box 102)
  - 1906-1909 (Box 103)
  - Committee of One Hundred, 1933 (Box 104)
  - Emeritus Reunions, 1938-1947 (Box 103)
  - Emeritus Club Reunions, 1948-1951 (Box 104)
  - Medical Alumni Reunion, 1931-1947 (Box 118)
- Class Officer and District Files, 1923-1953
  Class Officer and District Records (boxes 118-121) chronicle the developing organization of the Alumni Association as the organization grew. Documentation reflects efforts to promote the interests of the university, develop a large alumni network, increase interest in class reunions, and compile accurate information on alumni classes.
  - Class Officers Council Files, 1932-1950 (Box 118)
  - Class Officers Council Files, 1932-1950 (Box 119)
  - First District Records, 1932-1952 (Box 120)
  - First District Records, 1932-1952 (Box 121)
  - Second District Records, 1923-1939 (Box 121)
  - Tenth District Records, 1951-1953 (Box 121)
- Class Reunion Files, 1894-1963
  The Class Reunion Files (boxes 148-154) series spans the period 1924 to 1993 and contains information on classes from 1894 to 1963. The series is arranged by classes according to the years in which they graduated. Much of the material reflects the mechanics or organizing reunions, but news on class members and lists of former students are often present in these files.
  - 1894
    - Law, 1946 (Box 148)
  - 1898
    - Medical, 1938 (Box 148)
  - 1899
    - Law, 1944 (Box 148)
    - Medical, 1939 (Box 148)
  - 1900
    - Engineering & Literary, 1925; 1960-1961 (Box 148)
  - 1902
    - Engineering & Literary, 1963-1967 (Box 148)
  - 1903
    - Law, 1963 (Box 148)
  - 1904
    - Engineering, 1962-1967 (Box 148)
    - Law, 1964 (Box 148)
    - Literary, 1959-1964 (Box 148)
  - 1905
    - Engineering, 1956 (Box 148)
  - 1906
    - Engineering, 1960-1963 (Box 148)
    - Medical, 1941; 1946 (Box 148)
  - 1907
    - Engineering
      - General, 1961-1972 (Box 148)
      - Newsletters, 1953-1974; 3 folders (Box 148)
    - Law, 1963-1964 (Box 148)
  - 1908
    - Engineering, 1963-1968 (Box 148)
    - Literary, 1950-1968 (Box 148)
  - 1909
    - Engineering, 1959-1961 (Box 148)
  - 1911
    - Engineering, 1961-1974 (Box 148)
    - Law, 1961-1966 (Box 148)
    - Literary, 1960-1961 (Box 148)
    - Medical, 1960-1971 (Box 148)
  - 1912
    - Dental, 1957; 1962 (Box 148)
    - Engineering, 1961-1967 (Box 148)
    - Law, 1957-1962 (Box 148)
    - Literary, 1961-1967 (Box 148)
  - 1913
    - Engineering, 1958; 1963 (Box 148)
    - Law, 1963 (Box 148)
    - Literary, 1932; 1963 (Box 148)
  - 1914
    - Engineering, 1964-1972 (Box 148)
    - Law, 1964-1966 (Box 148)
    - Literary, 1964 (Box 148)
  - 1915
    - Dentistry, 1949-1965 (Box 148)
    - Engineering, 1954-1965 (Box 148)
    - Law, 1954 (Box 148)
    - Literary, 1939-1965 (Box 148)
  - 1916
    - Dentistry, 1960-1966 (Box 148)
    - Engineering, 1960-1971 (Box 148)
    - Law, 1936-1961 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1936-1961 (Box 149)
    - Medical, 1952 (Box 149)
  - 1917
    - Dentistry, 1957-1972 (Box 149)
    - Engineering, 1937-1972 (Box 149)
      (includes "Who's Who in Engineering")
    - Literary, 1930-1977 (Box 149)
  - 1918
    - Dentistry, 1953-1960 (Box 149)
    - Engineering, 1938-1978 (Box 149)
    - Law, 1947-1968 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1957-1968 (Box 149)
  - 1919
    - Dentistry, 1939-1974 (Box 149)
    - Engineering, 1958-1969 (Box 149)
    - Law, circa 1936; 1958 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1934-1969 (Box 149)
    - Medical, 1959-1964 (Box 149)
  - 1920
    - Engineering, 1940-1970 (Box 149)
    - Law, 1960-1970 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1960-1970 (Box 149)
  - 1921
    - Dentistry, 1960-1971 (Box 149)
    - Engineering & Architecture, 1945-1981 (Box 149)
    - Law, 1960-1971 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1961-1971 (Box 149)
  - 1922
    - Engineering, 1953-1982 (Box 149)
    - Law, 1952-1962 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1962-1972 (Box 149)
    - Medical, 1962-1963 (Box 149)
  - 1923
    - Dentistry, 1962-1978 (Box 149)
    - Engineering, 1961-1973 (Box 149)
    - Law, 1953-1983 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1958-1988 (Box 149)
    - Nursing, 1978 (Box 149)
  - 1924
    - Architecture, 1974 (Box 149)
    - Dentistry, 1964; 1974-1979 (Box 149)
    - Engineering, 1954-1983 (Box 149)
    - Law, 1924-1974 (Box 149)
    - Literary, 1964-1979 (Box 149)
  - 1925
    - Architecture, 1925 (Box 150)
    - Dentistry, 1960-1965 (Box 150)
    - Engineering, 1950-1985 (Box 150)
    - Law, 1960-1979 (Box 150)
    - Literary, 1960-1985 (Box 150)
    - Medical, 1960 (Box 150)
  - 1926
    - Architecture, 1966 (Box 150)
    - Dentistry, 1961-1986 (Box 150)
    - Engineering, 1964-1966 (Box 150)
    - Law, 1940-1981 (Box 150)
    - Literary, 1961-1976 (Box 150)
    - Medical, 1961-1966 (Box 150)
    - Nursing, 1971-1976 (Box 150)
  - 1927
    - Architecture, 1962-1976 (Box 150)
    - Dentistry, 1960-1977 (Box 150)
    - Engineering, 1962-1982 (Box 150)
    - Law, 1967-1987 (Box 150)
    - Literary, 1962-1982 (Box 150)
    - Nursing, 1977 (Box 150)
  - 1928
    - Business Administration, 1961-1993 (Box 150)
    - Dentistry, 1961-1978 (Box 150)
    - Engineering, 1967-1978 (Box 150)
    - Law, 1968-1978 (Box 150)
    - Literary, 1963-1983 (Box 150)
    - Medical, 1961-1988 (Box 150)
  - 1929
    - Business Administration, 1974; 1979 (Box 150)
    - Dentistry, 1964-1979 (Box 150)
    - Engineering, 1959-1989 (Box 150)
    - Law, 1963-1974 (Box 150)
    - Literary, 1964-1978 (Box 150)
    - Nursing, 1979 (Box 150)
  - 1930
    - Architecture, 1979-1980 (Box 150)
    - Dentistry, 1962-1980 (Box 150)
    - Engineering, 1980 (Box 150)
    - Law, 1960-1981 (Box 150)
    - Literary, 1960-1985 (Box 150)
    - Medical, 1963-1980 (Box 150)
    - Nursing, 1980 (Box 150)
  - 1931
    - Dentistry, 1961-1984 (Box 150)
    - Education, 1961-1981 (Box 150)
    - Engineering, 1941-1993 (Box 150)
    - Law, 1961-1986 (Box 150)
    - Literary, 1960-1981 (Box 150)
    - Medical, 1961-1981 (Box 150)
    - Nursing, 1981 (Box 150)
  - 1932
    - Architecture, 1981-1982 (Box 151)
    - Dentistry, 1962-1987 (Box 151)
    - Engineering
      - General, 1962-1982 (Box 151)
      - Personal Data Sheets, 1982 (Box 151)
    - Law, 1947; 1962-1982 (Box 151)
    - Literary, 1957-1982 (Box 151)
  - 1933
    - Dentistry, 1983 (Box 151)
    - Engineering, 1963-1992 (Box 151)
    - Law, 1963-1983 (Box 151)
    - Literary, 1969-1983 (Box 151)
    - Medical, 1958-1988 (Box 151)
  - 1934
    - Dentistry, 1960-1984 (Box 151)
    - Engineering, 1958-1984 (Box 151)
    - Literary, 1964-1974 (Box 151)
    - Medical, 1962-1964 (Box 151)
  - 1935
    - Dentistry, 1960-1985 (Box 151)
    - Engineering, 1937; 1960-1990 (Box 151)
    - Law, 1960; 1975-1985 (Box 151)
    - Literary, 1960-1990 (Box 151)
    - Medical
      - General, 1962-1990 (Box 151)
      - Questionnaires, 1965 (Box 151)
    - Music, 1960; 1980 (Box 151)
  - 1936
    - Business Administration, 1961 (Box 151)
    - Dentistry, 1961-1986 (Box 151)
    - Engineering, 1961-1991 (Box 151)
    - Law, 1950-1986 (Box 151)
    - Literary, 1961; 1984-1986 (Box 151)
    - Medical, 1961 (Box 151)
    - Engineering, 1962-1982 (Box 151)
    - Law, 1962-1982 (Box 151)
    - Literary, 1962-1987 (Box 151)
    - Medical, 1962-1987 (Box 151)
    - Nursing, 1972-1987 (Box 151)
  - 1937-38
    - Dentistry, 1960-1987 (Box 151)
  - 1938
    - Architecture, 1963-1973 (Box 152)
    - Engineering
      - Newsletter, 1939-1988; 2 folders (Box 152)
      - Personal Data Sheets, 1962 (Box 152)
    - Law, 1962; 1973-1988 (Box 152)
    - Literary, 1958-1988 (Box 152)
    - Medical, 1962-1988 (Box 152)
    - Nursing, 1978-1981 (Box 152)
  - 1939
    - Dentistry, 1960-1989 (Box 152)
    - Engineering, 1964-1989 (Box 152)
    - Law, 1964-1984 (Box 152)
    - Literary, 1964-1989 (Box 152)
    - Medical, 1979-1989 (Box 152)
    - Nursing, 1979-1989 (Box 152)
  - 1940
    - Architecture, 1950 (Box 152)
    - Dentistry, 1950-1990 (Box 152)
    - Education, 1946-1970 (Box 152)
    - Engineering, 1942-1980 (Box 152)
    - Law, 1946-1985 (Box 152)
    - Literary, 1950-1990 (Box 152)
    - Medical, 1965-1990 (Box 152)
    - Music, 1946 (Box 152)
    - Nursing, 1985 (Box 152)
  - 1941
    - Architecture, 1946-1951 (Box 152)
    - Business Administration, 1944 (Box 152)
    - Dentistry, 1946-1983 (Box 152)
    - Engineering, 1946-1991 (Box 152)
    - Law, 1947-1986 (Box 152)
    - Literary, 1961-1991 (Box 152)
    - Medical, 1956-1986 (Box 152)
    - Music, 1943-1945 (Box 152)
    - Nursing, 1971-1986 (Box 152)
  - 1942
    - Dentistry, 1957-1987 (Box 152)
    - Engineering, 1947-1992 (Box 152)
    - Law, 1945-1992 (Box 153)
    - Literary, 1944-1991 (Box 153)
    - Medical, 1946-1990 (Box 153)
    - Music, 1946-1947 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1968-1987 (Box 153)
  - 1943
    - Dentistry, 1955-1975 (Box 153)
    - Engineering
      - General, 1946-1993 (Box 153)
      - Personal Data Questionnaires
        - 1973 (Box 153)
        - 1978 (Box 153)
    - Literary, 1963-1993 (Box 153)
    - Medical, 1944-1988 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1968-1983 (Box 153)
  - 1943,1944,1945
    - Law, 1974-1989 (Box 153)
  - 1944
    - Dentistry, 1954-1964 (Box 153)
    - Engineering, 1959-1989 (Box 153)
    - Literary, 1959-1989 (Box 153)
    - Medical, 1959-1990 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1979-1984 (Box 153)
  - 1945
    - Dentistry, 1960-1965 (Box 153)
    - Engineering, 1960-1990 (Box 153)
    - Literary, 1960-1990 (Box 153)
    - Medical, 1965-1995 (Box 153)
    - NROTC, 1985-1990 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1970-1990 (Box 153)
  - 1946
    - Dentistry, 1961-1986 (Box 153)
    - Law, 1961 (Box 153)
    - Literary, 1959-1986 (Box 153)
    - Medical, 1966-1990 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1971-1986 (Box 153)
  - 1947
    - Engineering, 1962-1993 (Box 153)
    - Law, 1987 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1977-1986 (Box 153)
  - 1947-1948
    - Football Team, 1986 (Box 153)
  - 1948
    - Dentistry, 1960-1978 (Box 153)
    - Law, 1953-1983 (Box 153)
    - Literary, 1957-1973 (Box 153)
    - Medical, 1962-1988 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1978-1983 (Box 153)
    - Dentistry, 1984 (Box 153)
    - Engineering, 1974 (Box 153)
    - Law, 1958-1979 (Box 153)
    - Literary, 1964-1974 (Box 153)
    - Medical, 1979-1993 (Box 153)
    - Nursing, 1979-1984 (Box 153)
  - 1950
    - Architecture, 1975 (Box 154)
    - Business Administration, 1965 (Box 154)
    - Combined Classes, 1975-1993 (Box 154)
    - Dentistry, 1960-1990 (Box 154)
    - Law, 1960-1985 (Box 154)
    - Literary, 1960-1965 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1960-1990 (Box 154)
  - 1951
    - Business Administration, 1961-1981 (Box 154)
    - Dentistry, 1961-1991 (Box 154)
    - Engineering, 1961 (Box 154)
    - Law, 1952-1986 (Box 154)
    - Literary, 1961-1991 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1966-1986 (Box 154)
    - Nursing, 1971-1980 (Box 154)
  - 1952
    - Combined Classes, 1982-1992 (Box 154)
    - Dentistry, 1960-1987 (Box 154)
    - Law, 1962-1987 (Box 154)
    - Literary, 1961-1962 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1962-1987 (Box 154)
    - Nursing, 1957-1982 (Box 154)
  - 1953
    - Dentistry, 1962-1963 (Box 154)
    - Law
      - General, 1956-1964 (Box 154)
      - Personal Data Questionnaires, 1959 (Box 154)
  - 1954
    - Dentistry, 1964 (Box 154)
    - Law, 1962-1964 (Box 154)
  - 1955
    - Dentistry, 1960-1965 (Box 154)
    - Education, 1965 (Box 154)
    - Engineering, 1965 (Box 154)
    - Law, 1964-1965 (Box 154)
    - Literary, 1965 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1961-1965 (Box 154)
  - 1956
    - Dentistry, 1965-1966 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1966 (Box 154)
  - 1957
    - Dentistry, 1962-1965 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1962 (Box 154)
  - 1958
    - Law, 1962-1963 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1963 (Box 154)
  - 1959
    - Dentistry, 1964 (Box 154)
  - 1960
    - Dentistry, 1965 (Box 154)
    - Medical, 1965 (Box 154)
  - 1963
    - Law, 1973 (Box 154)
- Scrapbooks, Registers and Accounts, 1897-1986
  Scrapbooks, Registers, and Account Books (boxes 122-123; and 160) includes registers of alumni attending special events as well as scrapbooks pertaining to the special events such as the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd triennial meetings of the national University of Michigan clubs. Registers include alumni attending the 1904 Louisiana Purchase Exposition and the 1915 Panama-Pacific International Exposition. Account books include an Alumni Association day book and journal covering 1897-1907.
  - Account Books of Alumni Association, 1897-1906; 2 volumes (Box 122)
  - Account books, Michigan National dinner, New York, 1911; 2 volumes (Box 123)
  - Dental Hygienists Alumnae, 1954-1986; 3 volumes (Box 160)
  - Minutes of 3rd Triennial meeting of University of Michigan Clubs, 1931 (Box 122)
  - Notebooks concerning Alumni Clubs in Latin America, 1942-1946; 2 volumes (Box 123)
  - Register of Alumni attending Louisiana Purchase Exposition, 1904 (Box 123)
  - Register of Alumni at Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 1915 (Box 123)
  - Scrapbook, 1st Triennial meeting of University of Michigan Clubs, 1925 (Box 122)
  - Scrapbook, 2nd Triennial meeting of University of Michigan Clubs, 1928 (Box 122)
    (In Box 128)
  - Scrapbook concerning National Michigan dinner, Philadelphia, 1926 (Box 123)
  - Scrapbook of clippings concerning the University of Michigan Centennial Celebration, 1937 (Volume 1)
    (BImu/H1a)
- Society of Alumni, 1845-1897
  The Society of Alumni series (box 122) contains records of this precursor to the Alumni Association. The society was initially open to graduates of all the schools and colleges but eventually was defined as the alumni organization of the literary college. Often the society functioned as a coordinating body for the loose confederation of societies formed by the other schools and colleges while also administering the Williams Professorship Fund. Records of the society include minutes, 1859-1897, a receipt book, letter book, and assorted early records including a compilation of alumni news articles appearing in campus publication from 1845 to 1892. The minutes include necrology reports on members of the universities early classes. Also included is a minute book of the Medical Alumni Association covering 1875-1897.
  - Copies of News Articles, 1845-1892 (Box 122)
  - Letterbook, 1879-1887 (Box 122)
  - Medical Alumni Association, minute book, 1875-1897 (Box 122)
  - Minutes, 1859-1897 (Box 122)
  - Papers, 1859-1870 (Box 122)
  - Receipt book, 1879-1881 (Box 122)
  - Register of Alumni at Colombian Exposition, 1893; 2 volumes (Box 122)
    (one outsize vol. at BImu/H1a)
  - Zina P. King Letter, re. finances, 1890 (Box 122)
- Special Projects and Topics, 1909-2001
  The Alumni Association records (boxes 126-130; and 168) also include material on several Special Projects and Subjects. These records remain unprocessed but nonetheless contain a wealth of information on several significant projects and issues such as the planning and construction of Alumni Memorial Hall, Michigan Union, and the Michigan League. Four unprocessed boxes of Michigan League Building Fund Campaign Files from 1921 to 1926 are located in boxes 105-108. Material in boxes 126-129 includes background on the plans for a memorial to President Marion L. Burton ultimately resulting in construction of a carillon. Some of the other subjects include information on the Williams Professorship Fund used to support retired professors, the Michigan Alumnus, celebration of the 75th anniversary of the University of Michigan in 1912, opposition to the name change of Michigan State University from Michigan Agricultural College, alumni and scholarship funds, and faculty awards. Interspersed among these records are financial records of the Alumni Association. Material on the "Committee of One Hundred" in Box 104 relates to an effort to organize alumni to protest proposed cuts to university funding in 1933.
  - 75th anniversary of the University, 1912 (Box 129)
  - Alumni Advisory Board, 1909-1915 (Box 129)
  - Alumni Association Financial Records, 1932-1933; 3 volumes (Box 127)
  - Alumni Fund, 1920-1958 (Box 126)
  - Alumni Memorial Hall Committee, 1915 (Box 129)
  - Alumni Projects, 1937 (Box 127)
  - Copies of radio talks (Box 129)
  - District activities (Box 128)
  - Dormitories Corporation, 1922 (Box 129)
  - Fellowships and scholarships (Box 128)
  - Finances of the Alumni Association, 1911-1922 (Box 129)
  - Form letters and flyers concerning the Michigan Alumnus magazine (Box 127)
  - Glee Club Alumni, 1932-1951 (Box 127)
  - Marion Burton Memorial, 1925-1939 (Box 126)
  - Michigan Alumnus Advisory Board, 1922 (Box 129)
  - Michigan National Dinner in New York, 1911 (Box 129)
  - Michigan Union, 1911-1919 (Box 129)
  - Miscellaneous Projects, 1996-1999 (with gaps) (Box 168)
  - Miscellaneous subjects (Box 129)
  - Opposition to the Michigan State University name change, 1954-1956 (Box 127)
  - Responses to alumni questionnaire, 1927 (Box 130)
  - Scrapbook 2nd Triennial Meeting of the University of Michigan Club of Chicago, 1928 (Box 128)
  - Second district records (Box 128)
    (1981 accession; T. Maxwell Collier, donor)
  - Wade McCree Distinguished Faculty Award, 1991; undated (Box 168)
  - Williams Fund, 1897-1903 (Box 127)
- Topical Files, 1847-1994; undated
  The Topical Files series (boxes 157-159; 164-167; and 169) includes one item from 1847 but otherwise spans the period from 1909 to 1998. The files are alphabetically arranged and cover a wide array of topics. The 1847 item is a receipt for room rent issued to Charles Beckwith of the class of 1849. The Beckwith folder also includes a biographical sketch written in 1941. There is considerable information on scholarships, fellowships and funds supported by the Alumni Association and Alumnae Council. Several of the files on individual funds and endowments include information on who the fund or endowment is named after. Some student reminiscences are included within this series detailing university life prior to 1900. Also within this series are materials on student recruitment, career placement, and internship and mentorship programs.
  Notable files include material on the founding date of the university (located in the Frank Culver file), Milton Berger's description of Japanese surrender on Okinawa in 1945, and certificates chartering the first alumni club on the moon. The moon chapter folder contains information about the Apollo 15 space mission comprised of University of Michigan alumni James B. Irwin, David R. Scott, and Alfred M. Worden, Jr. Other notable files include a list of prominent minority alumni, and materials such as correspondence, reports, hearings and testimonies pertaining to racial incidents on U-M's campus.
  - Acacia Fraternity (Harlan Rowe), 1927 (Box 157)
  - Alumni Center, 1973-1982
    - Campaign Steering Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 157)
    - General and Dedication, 1973-1982; 2 folders (Box 157)
  - Alumni in Action, 1964 (Box 157)
  - Alumni Education, 1969-1970 (Box 157)
  - Alumni Memorial Hall, 1965-1966 (Box 157)
  - Beckwith, Charles (includes room receipt and biographical sketch), 1847 (Box 157)
  - Berger, Milton (World War II letter re: Okinawa), 1945 (Box 157)
  - Bishop, Frederick (reminiscences of student days), 1971-1982 (Box 157)
  - Black Action Movement, 1970 (Box 157)
  - Black Leadership Council, 1981-1982
    - Black Leadership Council, 1981-1982 (Box 157)
    - Proposed Articles of Procedure, 1981 (Box 169)
  - Board of Directors Committees, 1941-1967 (Box 157)
  - Board of Directors Meetings, 1897-1988 (scattered dates)
    - 1897-1947, 3 volumes (Box 166)
      Includes minutes of the Board of Directors.
    - 1947-1965, 4 volumes (Box 167)
      Includes minutes of meetings and reports to the Board of Directors and the Executive Committee of the Board of Directors; volumes for years 1957-1965 include munutes of the Budget and Finance Committee.
    - 1967-1988 (scattered dates) (Box 157)
  - Career Planning and Placement, 1989-1990; undated
    - Employment and Career Assistance Program Coordinating Committee, 1989; undated (Box 169)
    - Internship Opportunity Connection Project, 1990; undated (Box 169)
  - Chandler, George M. (re: University of Michigan alumni in the Civil War and military hospitals named for Michigan men) (Box 158)
  - Chicago Alumni 25th Annual Banquet, 1913 (Box 158)
  - Class Officers Council, 1927-1969; 9 folders (Box 158)
  - Class Secretaries List, 1871-1927 (Box 158)
  - Clubs Council, 1957-1984
    - Ad Hoc Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 158)
    - By-laws, 1981-1983 (Box 158)
    - Manual, 1957; 1974 (Box 158)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1975-1984 (Box 158)
  - Clubs Council District Reports, 1977-1984 (with gaps)
    - 1971 (Box 158)
      (9th district only)
    - 1977-1984, 4 folders (Box 158)
  - Comprehensive Studies Program, 1989-1994; undated (Box 169)
    - Collaborative Project, undated (Box 169)
    - Mentorship Program Board Meetings, 1989-1994; undated (Box 169)
  - Constitutional Convention Delegates (with UM ties), 1909-1960 (Box 158)